(Tsumura) Because of me, you and Kento were targeted.
(Yuri) Huh? What do you mean?
it is…
7 years ago we...
were supposed to get married
♬〜
what do you mean?
Me and... Tsumura-san?
Haha... that can't be true, right?
Because Yusuke and I...
Yusuke?
what did you do?
Huh?
What do you mean?
This guy is...
I'm a Neurovis person.
Did you mess with her memory too?
Huh?
lie
Yusuke...
That's a lie, right?
(Ninomiya) He's right.
Me and Yuri...
There was nothing
We're just classmates from elementary school who happened to meet again at university.
Sigh...
My… memories?
why?
It's for you
To keep you from becoming the wife of a murderer
I erased Tsumura's incident and his memory.
That's not all.
I didn't just erase my memory.
I rewritten the memories of me and Yuri into memories of you.
Did you do it on your own will?
Only I can rewrite memories
That's a technique I created.
So... Nanami Ishino's memories are also yours?
ah
Memories of Muroya too
Don't be silly, it's your fault!
What about the wise man? What about the wise man?
not my child
Huh?
Then... forever...
So you were cheating on me and Kento?
why?
To you...
I just wanted you to look at me
♬〜
《Hehe...》
《Together forever...》
《Let's be together》
《Let's go》
《Please be careful when you go》
♬〜
you are not the police
Not a wise father
I…
Not even the person I loved
Well then...
Who the hell are you?
It wasn't supposed to be like this...
(cry)
♬〜
Yuri
I should have told you sooner, but I was thinking about Yuri...
I can't believe anything anymore...
♬〜
Mom?
Sage...
ah…
good
It's okay, you did your best
(Sage) What about daddy?
dreamed
Mom and Dad... go to the sea park...
♬(3 people)《I'm hungry》
♬〜
Mom?
What about Muroya?
I ran away
What about your son?
it's okay
♬〜
It's stable
I think I'll wake up in about two days.
(Kousaka) Thank you
It's okay now
Muroya, please do something about it.
are you okay?
Yeah
Sorry for being late in telling you
Apparently they are growing well in that facility.
What happened?
Ninomiya was rewriting your memory.
yes…
finish it all
Kento... ah...
No... you did a great job.
Yeah
Good hahahaha
Kento: I'll go talk to Uncle Osamu in a bit.
Can you wait for me?
(Sage) Yeah
Why were you silent?
Tsumura-san and I were supposed to get married.
There's no way I didn't know
Did you know that my memories have been rewritten?
tell me what are you talking about
Yuri: You know... about your mother too.
Huh?
About when my mother died...
Even if I tried to remember, I couldn't remember
But when Kento was attacked, I only saw it for a moment.
Mom isn't sick...
He died in the fire, no, no...
I don't want to live without knowing the truth.
I don't need fake memories
please
♬〜
(Osamu) I was on my way home from the piano...
(Masami)《Did you play it for me? " "Yeah"
(Female)《Isn't it a fire after all? 》
《What should I do? What should I do?》 《What is it? 》
(Female)《Second floor? The fire...》
(Male)《I contacted you, right? 》 《Even if》
(Male) 《Not at all... yet? Firefighting》
(Female)《There is still a child inside》
(Male)《What? 》 (Female)《What should I do...》
《Yuri, wait a minute》 《Eh...》
(Male) 《Hey, what are you doing? 》
(Female)《No! " "mother! 》
"mother! 》
(Osamu) You blamed yourself.
Unless you say you want to learn piano...
If I had gone home alone without asking to be picked up...
If I had stopped my mother then...
(cry)
you stopped laughing
I wonder how I forgot about that...
Also… Yusuke?
Yeah, it's better to forget
You'll be happier if you don't know
That's what I thought
I'm sorry
What happened to the child that the mother tried to save?
I was saved
ah…
(Osamu) That's... Tsumura-kun.
This is the inmate list, and everything else I looked up.
(Takagishi) I can't believe it...
Can I make this into an article?
(cell phone vibration sound)
hello
📱(Tsujimoto) Tsumura-san! I found Muroya!
Yo
♬〜
Will you kill me again? (Tsujimoto) Tsumura-san, no!
You won't kill me, huh?
Testify.
I'll testify that my memory was rewritten.
presumed dead
I wonder what Neurovice has done to me.
♬〜
(Tsujimoto) Mr. Kosaka...
(Kousaka) What do you mean by giving him away?
There's no point in letting him testify.
Is it because you cover it up?
Do you mean higher than me?
You are also in danger
Then just forget everything
Are you telling me to cry myself to sleep?
I didn't say that
I also have no intention of continuing to obey the orders of those above me.
I need him for that
I want you to leave it to me
♬〜
(chime)
What about Mr. Ninomiya?
something?
no…
Mr. Tsumura is probably trying to make accusations about what has happened so far.
Ah... that's not the point
Let's help Ninomiya-san.
That's not why I came
He's... no more
Huh?
I just wanted you to look at me...
It's a little creepy
(Nanami) I wonder if she was planning to hide it all this time...
I think that's hard though.
♬〜
(Nanami) It's really weird.
I was fooled about Yusuke Ninomiya.
I'm actually so annoyed that I want to kill him...
I'm grateful to Masaki Igawa.
My memory is back...
I even remembered things I didn't want to remember
I didn't get along at all with my dead husband.
Is that so (Nanami)?
Man's luck...
...I don't think so. I don't have any luck.
I don't have any memories of being loved by anyone...not even by my parents.
But I felt love for you, didn't I?
He loved me properly
Well, that's also a memory made by Mr. Ninomiya.
But being loved by someone
Now that I know how happy I am, hehe
Ah...
daughter
♬〜
That's cute haha
I don't think you remember me.
But I'm thinking of showering this child with so much love that I hate it.
So much so that you start to hate me hehehehe
(sound of breathing)
Lastly, should I punch Ninomiya-san or just say thank you?
I came here thinking of doing something...
♬〜
I want to talk
It's all my fault
I was arrested...
I thought it would be better if I wasn't around Yuri anymore.
But it was a mistake, I ran away
Could you give me another chance?
I still think about Yuri... the one who loved me
Was it because of my mother?
I heard
Mr. Tsumura was the one who was saved from the fire that killed his mother.
After that, I spent some time counseling with Uncle Osamu.
I was receiving it, right?
Living comfortably at someone else's expense
I can't stand it anymore
So I feel responsible...
different! It's true that the first time I found out was that person's daughter.
I had mixed feelings, but as I learned more
I really started to like Yuri.
this is not a lie
sorry
Why Yuri... I'm the one who should apologize.
Because of me, your mother... I'm sorry.
Is that why you covered me? Huh?
I can't remember anything.
But... this is all I know.
I…
That Muroya punched a man.
Sorry Yuri!
It's enough that your life was ruined because of me!
What do you like?
you loved me
But I don't have that memory.Even if I try to remember, I can't.
Even if I was told the truth, I still...
still…
I have nothing but happy memories with Yusuke.
What should I do?
♬〜
sorry
Please stop it
♬〜
Ninomiya-san, I'm glad you're back (Rie) Ah...
Instead you'll be blown away
Huh? why?
You made a photo of the Igawa couple, right?
(Researcher) Yes
Masaki Igawa's fingers were strangely extended
No, that was an AI mistake... Huh? Ah...
Open it! Open it!
(unlock sound)
♬〜
Ugh...
It's all your fault... it's all your fault!
So what should I do?
That day, Yuri was on the verge of breaking down.
《Ah》
《Welcome back》 《Welcome back》
《I'll take it》 《Yeah, take it, hehehehe》
《Can I take a bath first? 》
《Yeah, I'll make food right away.》 《Thank you.》
《Ugh... ah...》
(Murotani)《Is that his woman? Then it starts with you.
《(coughing)》
《Ah... Dai-chan! 》
♬〜
"ah! 》
《Ah...》
《(Rough breathing)》
♬〜
《Yuri? 》
《Yuri! 》
♬〜
(Murotani)《I have memorized your face, so be prepared when it appears》
``What happened? 》
《What about Yuri? " "it's okay"
《I just fainted from shock》
《This is the man I arrested》
《He came to take revenge on me》
《(Sigh)》
《I... will turn myself in》
《Can I ask you something about Yuri? 》 《What? 》
《Tell them I'll pretend the engagement never happened》
《No, that’s it...》
《I don't want Yuri to become the wife of a criminal.》
《If something happens, please protect Yuri instead of me》
"ask"
♬〜
"got it"
《Ha… ha…》
♬〜
《It's okay now》
《Where is this? 》
《Ninomiya-kun, why? 》
《What about Dai-chan? 》
♬〜
《Ah...》
《(breathing heavily)》 《Fujitani-san! 》
"no! 》
♬〜
《Who is that man? 》
《It's okay now》 《What? 》
《I hit you》 《What? 》
《I'm bleeding... I'm dizzy...》
《When you realize...》
《What about Dai-chan? What about Dai-chan? 》
《To the police...》 《What? 》
《He turned himself in》
♬〜
《Like that...》
"different…"
《Wait, wait, wait! 》
《Let me go! " "different! 》
``I hit you! 》 《Because it's different! 》
``I killed it! 》 《Tsumura-san protected you! 》
"that's why…"
"Also…"
《Again... because of me...》
"(cry)"
"why! why! 》
"why! 》
I thought it would be better if you just disappeared
In order for Yuri to be happy...
you were in the way
Why did you come back in front of me and Yuri?
I understand
I knew it was all my fault.
I shouldn't have met Yuri.
I shouldn't have loved Yuri
Please turn it off
About Yuri from within me
Please erase me from Yuri once again.
Everything... just pretend it never happened.
Let me finish it
ask
♬〜
Understood
(cell phone vibration sound)
Which one is here?
Is this the place you and Tsumura used to come to often?
no…
The two of us came here for the first time.
I see.
I heard about the fire from my uncle.
You erased everything about your mother.
I wanted Yuri to keep smiling.
Forever, forever...
I loved Yuri
♬〜
《What? 》 《I'll lend it to you》
(Student)《My mother died in a fire》
"He died because of Fujitani-san, right?"
(Student)《You're going to transfer, right?》
(Student)《He said he was going to visit a relative's uncle.》
♬〜
《Because I will help you...》
《(knock)》 (ji) 《please》
"uncle"
《Are you happy with this? 》 《Oh, this, this, this, this.》
《No, I was saved》
《I thought I put it in my bag.》
“I’m glad you emailed me before I left home.”
《Thank you》 《Hehehehe》
《Ah, that's right, Ninomiya-kun is there》
《He went to the same elementary school as Yuri.》
《What? Is it Asukagawa Elementary School? " "Yeah"
《Ninomiya-kun...》
《Ah... yeah》
"long time no see"
《Aaah》 《Eh, which one? 》
《Soba》 《Soba? 》
《Soba is delicious》 《Daichan》
《Good job》 《Ah Ninomiya-kun》
《We were in the same class when we were in elementary school, and now we are staying with Uncle Osamu...》
《Is it brain research? 》 《Yes, it's Ninomiya》
《This is Tsumura》
《Daichan was my tutor when I was in high school.
You'll be a police officer next year, right?
《Hehe, that's amazing》
《It's not great at all》 《It's amazing》
《Yuri is amazing every day...》
As long as Yuri is happy, that's fine.
《Because of me...》
"why! 》
"(cry)"
If only Yuri would smile
I...
I don't want to conveniently forget only sad things.
That's not me
It's you, no
No... it's not different.
You have to be happier than anyone else
More than anyone...
I was happy
About the day I spent with Yusuke and Kento.
I can't forget even if I want to forget
Even if I want to remember the days without you...
I can't remember
I still love you
But I can't forgive
I hate you!
Yuri, please don't cry. You don't have to be sad anymore.
I don't want you to be sad anymore
If it was for that purpose, I would do anything...
♬〜
thank you
Thank you for loving me
♬〜
(cry)
(Nanami) I don't know what I like...
I made so many
I'll teach you a lot from now on, hehehe
♬〜
delicious?
Hehehe, good, good
♬〜
Murotani was treated as unidentified (Uemoto) Yeah.
(Kosaka) A reporter who was trying to publicize the PS program
There was, but I stopped that too.
Thank you, please give me the information on that reporter (Kousaka) Yes.
Also... Nanami Ishino's data has been deleted.
What do you do without permission?
I will also be involved in selecting candidates for the PS program in the future.
♬〜
Was it good? About Yuzuki-chan...
I'm Sakura Ono. Thank you.
i like ramen
(Kousaka) If that girl is happy, I don't need her in her life.
♬〜
(Rie) Today is the borrowed race that everyone has been waiting for!
It's better to play rock, paper, scissors with the neighbors and buy it from Kame-san's team.
The one who loses is the lizard team.
(Aina) Now that I think about it, I started playing Borrowed Races.
It was Mr. Igawa, right? Yeah...
How are you doing?
I got a call the other day saying I'm doing great.
Is it true? good
A new person will be coming in to replace Igawa next week.
Yay! I see, I see.
Can I leave this to you? yes
♬〜
(Mitsuru) "If there's anything you don't understand, just ask."
"thank you"
(Takako) “We take a walk around here every day.”
"I definitely walk around 10,000 steps a day." "That's amazing."
(Mitsuru) "Actually, it's about 6,000 steps."
(Takako) "That's enough for 10,000 steps."
(Mitsuru) “Then 5,000 steps is fine.”
♬〜
(Sage) Papa!
yeah? (Sage) Look, Dangomushi.
Yeah! Oh no, Dad, I'm afraid of insects.
Hey! Wow, the dumpling bug is so cute.
That's so cool. There are so many things I don't like. I can't even eat cucumbers.
Cucumbers are now ready to eat!
Don't brag...
♬〜
Yes, no problem, I'll be back now.
(Kento) I love you hahahaha I love you too
(Yuri/Tsumura) Hahahaha
♬(Sage) Let's go home Let's go home I'm hungry.
Ah, I heard that for the first time in a while.
(Sage) Seino...
♬(Tsumura, Kento, Yuri) Let's go home, let's go home, I'm hungry.
♬Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home Let's go home
♬〜